[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "red",
        "back": "красный",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "cat",
        "back": "кошка",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "orange",
        "back": "апельсин",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "dog",
        "back": "собака",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "black",
        "back": "черный",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "yellow",
        "back": "желтый",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "cow",
        "back": "корова",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "purple",
        "back": "фиолетовый",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "banana",
        "back": "банан",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "p",
        "back": "абзац",
        "setName":"tags"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "a",
        "back": "ссылка",
        "setName":"tags"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "front": "img",
        "back": "картинки",
        "setName":"tags"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "front": "border",
        "back": "контур",
        "setName":"css"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "front": "radius",
        "back": "радиус",
        "setName":"css"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "front": "color",
        "back": "цвет",
        "setName":"css"
    }
]